

CONTACT

+358 0449239180

✓ tsranathunga@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/th araka-ranathunga-58ba52205/

https://github.com/TharakaRana thunga

Yanga Kivikatu 5 B 51, 15700, Lahti

SKILLS

Team Player

Public Relations

Time Management

Leadership

Effective Communication

Problem Solving

ICT SKILLS

Microsoft Office HTML, CSS & Java Script Python Basic

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Sinhala (Mother tongue)

English (Fluent)

Chinese (Good)

Japanese (Good)

Finnish (Basic)

TKT CLIL - Band 4

PTE - 78

HSK Level 4

JLPT Level 3

CERTIFICATES

Hygiene Passport

THARAKA RANATHUNGA

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated professional with a proven track, a strong team player who thrives on collaboration, and a committed learner who takes up challenges. At the same time, a hard worker who always tries to complete the responsibilities taking the optimum output in providing the industry with the best production with knowledge, expertise and research.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Cleaner (Part-Time) InHouse Partners Oy, Lahti 01/11/2024 - Present, Lahti
- Advertisement Distributor (Part-Time) SSM Oy 28/08/2024 - Present. Lahti
- Lecturer Sabaragamuwa University of Sri Lanka
 03/05/2020 30/06/2024 Belihuloya, Sri Lanka
- Instructor Sri Lanka International Buddhist Academy 15/01/2018 - 30/04/2020 Colombo, Sri Lanka

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Engineering in Industrial Information Technology LAB University of Applied Sciences, Lahti, Finland 15/08/2024 - Present
- Master of Arts in Linguistics University of Kelaniya, Sri Lanka 19/04/2019-01/05/2023
- Bachelor of Arts (Special) Chinese
 Sabaragamuwa University of Sri Lanka
 16/07/2013 10/11/2017
- Certificate in Computer Science
 National Institute of Business Management, Sri Lanka
- Content and Language Integrated Learning
 Australian College of Business and Technology, Sri lanka
- Diploma in Airline Ticketing International Airline Ticketing Academy, Sri Lanka

INTERESTS

- Frontend Coding
- Backend Coding
- · Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning
- Database Management